ALLISON ROSENBERG

123 Carpenter Street, Philadelphia, PA, 12345 allisonrosenberg@exampie.com (123) 456*7890 A Marketing Coordinator with entry-level experience specializing in social media marketing, brand messaging, copywriting, and storytelling. Adept at crafting compelling content to enhance the impact of marketing campaigns and drive engagement with target audiences.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

MARKETING COORDINATOR

The Fillmore. Philadelphia, PA I May 2021 - Present

- ♦ Coordinate with the marketing team to manage social media platforms for an upscale music venue, conduct post scheduling using Hootsuite, and identify opportunities to refine marketing copy, resulting in a 300% increase in user engagement on Twitter
- Grow Facebook and Twitter followership by 250% over six months by creating and releasing social media posts during peak hours
- Write web marketing copy for the monthly newsletter and landing page and provide contributions to the company music blog

MARKETING INTERN

Fishtown Magazine, Philadelphia, PA I January 2021 - May 2021

- Wrote 15 blog posts for an online magazine covering various aspects of Philadelphian subcultures, art, music, and communities, including a piece detailing the unique cultural experience of growing up Jewish in South Philadelphia
- Provided recommendations to the marketing team to enhance voice and brand messaging on Twitter and Facebook social media accounts

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ARTS (B.A.) MARKETING

Temple University, Philadelphia, PA I September 2017 - May 2021

KEY SKILLS

- Social Media Marketing
- ♦ Copywriting
- ♦ Brand Messaging
- Marketing Strategy
- Audience Engagement